[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which breed is known for is know for its spotted coat and beloved Disney animated movie?", 
      "answer": "Dalmation"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "This breed is know for its very curly coat",
      "answer": "Poodle"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "This breed is know for its long, shiny coat",
      "answer": "Shih Tzu"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which breed is well known for its unique blue-black tounge?",
      "answer": "Chow Chow"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which breed is known for its powerful sense of smell?",
      "answer": "Bloodhound"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "This breed is one of America's most popular dog breeds and sports a golden coat.",
      "answer": "Golden Retriever"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What breed is known for its love for the snow and sled-pulling skills?",
      "answer": "Husky"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "This dog is often called a \"wiener dog\"!",
      "answer": "Dachsund"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "This breed is known for helping herd sheep",
      "answer": "Border Collie"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which dog is known for its pointy ears and hunting skills?",
      "answer": "German Shepherd"
    }
]